Finding Aid to the San Francisco Department of Public Health AIDS Office records SFH 4
San Francisco History Center, San Francisco Public Library
- Administrative Records, 1982-1994; Record Group 1; 22 Cubic Feet
  - Directors' Files, Subgroup 1; 13.1 Cubic Feet
    - Director's Office, San Francisco Department of Public Health, 1982-1990; Series 1; 2.1 Cubic Feet
      - Director Dr. David Werdegar, 1985-1990; Subseries 1.2
        - Subject Files
          - Amory, Jeff (Box 1, Folder 15)
          - Antibody Testing (Box 1, Folder 16)
          - AZT (Box 1, Folder 17)
          - Bathhouses (Box 1, Folder 18)
          - Blood Banks (Box 1, Folder 19)
          - Board of Supervisors, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
          - Chen, Robert T: Paper, Testimony (Box 1, Folder 21)
          - Children (Box 1, Folder 22)
          - Client Issues (Box 1, Folder 23)
          - Community Research Alliance (Box 1, Folder 24)
          - Compound Q (Box 1, Folder 25)
          - Condoms (Box 1, Folder 26)
          - Contact Tracing (Box 1, Folder 27)
          - Correspondence, [1988]-1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
          - Dementia Study (Box 1, Folder 29)
          - Director's Medical Advisory Group, June 1987 - February 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
          - Discrimination, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
          - Earthquake, October 17, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
          - Education/Prevention, 1988 - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
          - Education/Prevention: Policies in City Offices, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
          - Funding and Fundraising (Box 1, Folder 35)
          - Grants (Box 1, Folder 36)
          - Health Commission Issues, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
          - HIV Consensus Meeting, October 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
          - Hospitals (Box 1, Folder 39)
          - Housing (Box 1, Folder 40)
          - Immigration (Box 1, Folder 41)
          - Infection Control, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 42-43)
          - Legal Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 44)
          - Lesbian/Gay Health Services, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Medi-Cal (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Mid-City Consortium/YES (Box 2, Folder 3-7)
          - Minority Issues, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
          - Miscellaneous
          - Needle Exchange (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Nursing Issues (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - Planning for High Risk Gay Men, SFAF, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Presidential Commission on HIV Epidemic (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Prevention and I.V. Drug Use, Conference, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Prevention and Treatment, Framework for Local Planning, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Proposition 96 (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - Public Health Service Hospital Plan: Reactivation Master Plan (Box 2, Folder 16)
          - Recreation Center for Handicapped (Box 2, Folder 17)
          - Red Cross (Box 2, Folder 18)
          - Schools: AIDS Education, HIV+ Students, and Policies (Box 2, Folder 19)
          - SFDPH Orientation Manual (Box 2, Folder 20)
          - Shanti: Jim Geary Issue (Box 2, Folder 21)
          - Skilled Nursing Facilities (Box 2, Folder 22)
          - Substance Abuse Issues (Box 2, Folder 23)
          - Tenderloin AIDS Network (Box 2, Folder 24)
          - Testing (Box 2, Folder 25)
          - Unsafe Sex, Complaints of (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Director's Office, AIDS Office, 1982-1994; Series 2
      Arranged in six series: Series 3: Director Dr. George Rutherford; Series 4: Director Sandra Hernandez; Series 5: Assistant Director James Loyce; Series 5: Staff Meetings and Retreats; Series 6: Advisory Groups, Committees, Caucuses, and Councils; Series 7: Center for Positive Care (CPC).
      - Director Dr. George Rutherford, 1982-1990; Subseries 2.1
        FIles are arranged by topic, then chronologically.
        - Development of [AIDS] Informational Pamphlets, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - Connant Proposes Public Health Hosp as Regional AIDS Treatment Center, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - State Funding of AIDS Education, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - AIDS Activities Office; Mission and Description, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - AIDS Activities Office; Info Given to Board of Supervisors, January 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Documents Prepared for NYC AIDS Task Force visit to San Francisco, January 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Medical, Social & Financial Needs of [PWAs] in SF; A Pilot Survey, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - MASH (Minimizing AIDS Spread Heteros) Developing HIV Testing Info, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - San Francisco's Response To AIDS, SFDPH, October 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - [AIDS} in California;...Meeting the Needs of 1990, State DPH, March 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Funding For AIDS; Summary Information, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - AIDS Services at Health Center One, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - Organizational Charts, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - Stray Memos, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence From Visitors, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - Jeff Amory; Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        - Jeff Amory's Phone Messages, October 1985 - January 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
        - Long-term Survivors Protocol, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        - Office Spaces (1111 Market and 25 Van Ness), Searches & Moves, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
        - Nonprofit Sector's Response to AIDS Epidemic: Community-based Services in San Francisco by Peter Arno, American Journal of Public Health, November 1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        - "Map of AIDS' Deadly March Evolves From Hepatitis Study" Washington Post, February 1, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 24)
        - AIDS Office Confidentiality Policy Draft, circa 1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - AIDS Prevention: Developing the SF Model, Sam Puckett, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
        - AIDS Plan, 1986; 9 folders (Box 3, Folder 27-35)
          General
          9 folders
        - Reorganization of AIDS Office, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
        - Development of Black and Latino Surveys, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
        - Community Intervention Trial, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
        - Agency Monitoring Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
        - Correspondence to Dr. George Rutherford, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 40-41)
        - Testimony of Dr. George Rutherford, 1987, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 42)
        - VIP Visitors to AIDS Office, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 43)
        - Lesbian / Gay Parades, 1989, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
        - Development of Community AIDS Advisory Committees, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 45)
        - Director's Report to Health Commission, June 1989 (Box 3, Folder 46)
        - Proposition 102, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 47)
        - Proposition 96, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 48)
        - Photographs: Staff, Office, Retreats (Box SFH 4)
          Materials Transferred
          Photographs transferred to the San Francisco Historical Photograph Collection.
        - Photographic Negatives (Box SFH 4)
        - Photograph, matted 8 x 10 of AO Staff at 1989 Retreat (Box SFH 4)
        - AIDS Office Policies and Procedures, circa 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - Complaints From The Public (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - 1988-1989 Contract Negotiations - General (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - CCSF AIDS Plan, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Contractor Contacts (Meetings, etc.) (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Cross-Cultural Training (Box 4, Folder 6)
        - Earthquake ( 1989) After-effects (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Reception; Jeff Amory's Retirement, January 1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - Reception; George Rutherford Leaves and Sandra Hernandez becomes Director of AIDS Office, February 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Director Dr. Sandra Hernandez, 1985-1994; Subseries 2.2
        Further divided into nine nested files: Reports and Other Information; Correspondence; Notes; Budget and Planning; Center for Positive Care; External Meetings and Conferences; Subject Files; Organizations and Agencies; and 4.9: Troubleshooting Files.
        - Reports and Other Information, 1990-1991
          - File List, Executive Files (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Mission and History of AIDS Office (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Appointment Books, 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
          - Health Services Branch, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
          - Prevention Branch, January 1990 - December 1990 (Box 4, Folder 14-16)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1992
          - CHRON Files, January 1990 - December 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17-19)
          - HRS Branch, 1990, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 20)
          - HRS Management, 1989, 1992 (Box 4, Carton 21)
          - Operations, 1990, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
          - Prevention, 1990, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
          - Research, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
          - Surveillance, 1990, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
          - Memos and Letters, May - June 1990 (Box 4, Folder 26)
        - Notes, 1990-1992
          - Prevention Branch, 1990-1991, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
          - Health Services Branch, 1990-1991, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 28-29)
          - Surveillance Branch, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 30-34)
          - Operations Branch, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 35)
          - Research Branch, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
          - Unidentified Notes, circa 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
        - Budget and Planning, 1985-1992; Box 5
          - County Health Services Plan Update and Budget for City & County of San Francisco, FY 1985-1986 - 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 3-7)
          - AIDS in San Francisco: Status Report and Plan for FY 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 8)
          - AIDS in San Francisco: Status Report for 87/88 and Projections of Needs and Costs for 1988-93 (Box 5, Folder 9)
          - AIDS Services in San Francisco for FY 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
          - AIDS Services SFDPH Annual Report and AIDS Budget Priorities, 1988-1989, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 11)
          - AIDS Prevention and Health Care Services in San Francisco and Annual Report 1988-1989, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
          - AIDS in San Francisco: A Five Year Strategic Plan for Managing the Epidemic 1990-95 (Draft) (Box 5, Folder 13)
          - Guidelines for Contractors AIDS Office, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
          - Summary of AIDS Funding Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
            These relate to Ad Valorem Funding Issues for SFDPH.
          - AIDS Plan FY 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
          - AIDS Office Budget Files, 1991/1992, 1992/1993 Priorities (Box 5, Folder 17)
          - 1992-1993 General Fund Proposed Cuts (Box 5, Folder 18)
          - Subvention (STATE) (Box 5, Folder 19)
          - State Block Grant 1988/1989 - 1991/1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
          - History of AIDS Funding (Galen Leung) (Box 5, Folder 21)
          - Ambulance Care for HIV infected Individuals, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 22)
          - AIDS Financing / Cost (Box 5, Folder 23)
          - Long Term Care (Skilled Nursing Facility Hospital, etc) (Box 5, Folder 24)
          - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 25)
        - Center for Positive Care
          Related Materials
          Additional CPC materials are in Series 8: Center for Positive Care.
          - CPC (Box 5, Folder 26)
          - CPC Executive Director Meetings - Minutes (Box 5, Folder 27)
          - Evaluation of CPC by Rani Marx, February 1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
          - CPC Monitoring Reports (Box 5, Folder 29)
          - Alternative Testing Services (ATS) at CPC (Box 5, Folder 30)
          - S. Hernandez's: CPC Binder: Bound pages (Box 5, Folder 31)
          - S. Hernandez's: CPC Binder: Loose papers (Box 5, Folder 32)
        - External Meetings, Conferences, Etc., 1990-1992
          - American Association of Physicians for Human Rights (AAPHR) / Bay Area Physicians for Human Rights (BAPHR) Symposium, August 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
          - HIV+ Homeless Youth, June 26, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
          - Latino Providers Retreat, August 1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
          - Public Health Service: Minority AIDS/HIV Conference, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        - Subject Files, 1982-1992
          Alphabetical by topic.
          - Adolescents and AIDS (Box 6, Folder 5)
          - Affirmative Action; Investigative Reports, March 1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
          - Affirmative Action; Workforce Utility Analysis, February 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
          - African Leaders Investigative Visit to San Francisco, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
          - AIDS Cases by Race and Ethnicity, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
          - AIDS Office (25 Van Ness) Expansion, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
          - All American City Award - AIDS Office Portrayal, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
          - Campus Treatment (Substance Abuse) Demonstration Proposal (Box 6, Folder 12)
          - CEO's Public and Private Efforts, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
          - Community Liaison Chris Sandoval, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
          - Concern for Dying (Box 6, Folder 15)
          - Continuum of Care: Consensus Report, Needle Exchange, Prevention, December 1991, April 1992 (Box 6, Folder 16-18)
          - Continuum of Care: Primary Care (1989, 1991, 1992 Reports), April 1992 (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
          - Counseling Immigrants About HIV (Box 6, Folder 22)
          - Department of Social Services (Box 6, Folder 23)
          - Determining Service Needs and Priorities (Box 6, Folder 24)
          - Drug Program (AIDS Treatment), 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
          - Early Intervention, Candidates (Box 6, Folder 26)
          - Early Intervention, National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (NTFAP) (Box 6, Folder 27)
          - Educational Materials Review Process (Box 6, Folder 28)
          - Educational Tool: Smart Kids (Game) (Box 6, Folder 29)
          - EEO Training, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 30)
          - Hospice Care (Box 6, Folder 31)
          - Hospital Care for HIV/AIDS in West Bay, 1982-1989 (Box 6, Folder 32)
          - Housing for People With AIDS (PWAs) (Box 6, Folder 33)
          - Immigration Law and HIV (Box 6, Folder 34)
          - Knowledge, Attitudes, Beliefs, and Behaviors (KABBs); People of Color Communities (Box 6, Folder 35)
          - Knowledge, Attitudes, Beliefs, and Behaviors (KABBs), General Information (Box 6, Folder 36)
          - Latino AIDS, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 37)
          - Lesbian/Gay Health Services (Box 6, Folder 38)
          - LIFE Center (Box 6, Folder 39)
          - Mayor's Office: Client Eligibility Requirements (Box 6, Folder 40)
          - Mayor's Office: HIV and Youth, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 41)
          - Mayor's Office: Meetings with [People of Color] (Box 6, Folder 42)
          - National Minority AIDS Council, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 43)
          - Needle Exchange, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 44)
          - Nitrates (Poppers) (Box 6, Folder 45)
          - Office Parties, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 46)
          - Orientation Packets, 1990, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 47)
          - Orphan Drug Act (Box 6, Folder 48)
          - Prevention Program in SF (from 1991 CDC Grant) (Box 6, Folder 49)
          - Proposal for Prevention Initiative Geared Towards Gay/Bi Men of Color (Box 6, Folder 50)
          - Residential Housing for PWAs - Eviction Policies (Box 6, Folder 51)
          - Sexual Transmission of HIV (Box 6, Folder 52)
          - United Way of the Bay Area; Needs Assessment, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 53)
          - Women Organized to Respond to Life-Threatening Diseases (WORLD) (Box 6, Folder 54)
          - Women's Utilization of AIDS Services and Programs in San Francisco (Box 6, Folder 55)
        - Organizations and Agencies, 1987-1991
          Alphabetical by name of organization or agency.
          - AIDS/ARC Vigil (Box 7, Folder 1)
          - AIDS Benefits Counselors (Box 7, Folder 2)
          - American Red Cross (Box 7, Folder 3)
          - Asian AIDS Project (Box 7, Folder 4)
          - Asian American Recovery Service (Box 7, Folder 5)
          - Association for Women's AIDS Research and Education (AWARE) (Box 7, Folder 6)
          - BAART (Box 7, Folder 7)
          - Bayview-Hunter's Point Foundation (Box 7, Folder 8)
          - Coalition for Immigrant & Refugee Rights and Services (Box 7, Folder 9)
          - Community Consortium (Box 7, Folder 10)
          - Community Research Alliance (Box 7, Folder 11)
          - Community Treatment Advocacy Program (Box 7, Folder 12)
          - Community United Against Violence (Box 7, Folder 13)
          - Continuum (Box 7, Folder 14)
          - Communidad Unida en Respuesta Al Sida (CURAS) (Box 7, Folder 15)
          - Early Advocacy and Care for HIV (EACH), 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
          - Eighteenth Street Services, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
          - ENE Advertising (ENE), 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
          - Family Survival Project (Box 7, Folder 19)
          - Filipino Task Force on AIDS (Box 7, Folder 20)
          - GAPA Community HIV Project, October 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
          - Garden Sullivan Hospital, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
          - Glide AIDS Project, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 23)
          - Haight-Ashbury Free Clinic, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
          - Health Outreach Team, November 1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
          - Hospice By the Bay, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 26)
          - Instituto Familiar de la Raza (Box 7, Folder 27)
          - Interreligious Coalition on AIDS (Box 7, Folder 28)
          - Kaiser Patient Advocacy Union (Box 7, Folder 29)
          - La Clinica de la Raza (Box 7, Folder 30)
          - Latino AIDS Project, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
          - Latino Coalition on AIDS/SIDA, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 32)
          - Minority AIDS Project (MAP) (Box 7, Folder 33)
          - Mission Neighborhood Health Center (Box 7, Folder 34)
          - Multicultural Prevention Resource Center (MPRC) (Box 7, Folder 35)
          - National Native American AIDS Prevention Center (Box 7, Folder 36)
          - Operation Concern (Box 7, Folder 37)
          - Peter Claver Community (Box 7, Folder 38)
          - Polaris (Box 7, Folder 39)
          - Project Inform (Box 7, Folder 40)
          - Real Alternatives Program, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 41)
          - S.F. Community Clinic Consortium, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 42)
          - Shanti (Box 7, Folder 43)
          - Shanti HIV Treatment Advocacy Position Shanti Project (Box 7, Folder 44)
          - Shanti Project Multicultural Plan (Box 7, Folder 45)
          - St. Luke's Hospital (Box 7, Folder 46)
          - STOP AIDS Project (Box 7, Folder 47)
          - Walden House (Box 7, Folder 48)
          - The Wedge Program (aka Wedge Project or WEDGE), 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 49)
          - Youth Advocates, May 1992 (Box 7, Folder 50)
          - Youth Environment Services, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 51)
        - Troubleshooting Files, [1990?]-1994
          Mostly Hernandez files, with some later Directors' files interfiled according to issue/date.
          - AIDS Health Project (Box 7, Folder 52)
          - AIDS Indigent Direct Services (Box 7, Folder 53)
          - American Indian AIDS Institute (Box 7, Folder 54)
          - Bayview Hunters Point Foundation (Box 7, Folder 55)
          - Black Coalition on AIDS (Box 7, Folder 56)
          - CAL-PEP (Box 7, Folder 57)
          - Community Substance Abuse Services (Box 7, Folder 58)
          - Continuum (Box 7, Folder 59)
          - ENE Advertising (ENE) (Box 7, Folder 60)
          - GAPA Community HIV Project (Box 7, Folder 61)
          - Health Outreach Team (HOT), 1993-1994
            - Standards: Quality Assurance, Infection Control, Nurse Practitioner Protocols, Operating Manual (Box 7, Folder 62)
            - Case Management Contract, 5/93-4/94 (Box 7, Folder 63)
            - Audit and Special Investigation, 8/93-10/93 (Box 7, Folder 64)
            - General Correspondence and Documents, 6/91-8/93 (Box 7, Folder 65)
            - General Correspondence and Documents, 9/93-1/94 (Box 7, Folder 66)
          - Instituto Familiar de la Raza (Box 8, Folder 1)
          - Mental Health (Cohort Study) (Box 8, Folder 2)
          - Mission Neighborhood Health Center (Box 8, Folder 3)
          - National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (Box 8, Folder 4)
          - Pacific Presbyterian Medical Center (Box 8, Folder 5)
          - Planned Parenthood (Box 8, Folder 6)
          - Project Open Hand (Box 8, Folder 7)
          - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Box 8, Folder 8)
          - Sex Clubs and Public Sex, 1987-1992 (Box 8, Folder 9)
          - Shanti (Box 8, Folder 10-13)
          - St Mary's Hospital (Box 8, Folder 14)
          - Tenderloin AIDS Network (Box 8, Folder 15)
          - Urban Health Study (IPS) (Box 8, Folder 16)
          - WEDGE (Box 8, Folder 17)
          - Departmental AIDS Committee, 1986
            Folder listed on legacy finding aid but not found in the collection.
      - Assistant Director James Loyce, 1987-1993; Subseries 2.3
        Further divided into two nested file groups:General Files; and 5.2: Troubleshooting Files.
        - General Files, 1989-1993
          - Organization of AIDS Office; Charts, Narrative, Budget, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
          - Policies & Procedures, AIDS Office (Box 8, Folder 19)
          - Space Plan, AIDS Office (Box 8, Folder 20)
          - Memos, 1989-1992 (Box 8, Folder 21)
          - Operations Branch (Box 8, Folder 22)
          - Maria Lemus, Director of Operations Branch (Box 8, Folder 23)
          - Operations Branch Reorganization, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
          - Grants Management, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
          - Tracking System for AIDS Office Contracts (Box 8, Folder 26)
          - Recommended Changes in DPH Contract Policies - Troubleshooting File (Box 8, Folder 27)
          - Contracts - Lino Martinez (Box 8, Folder 28)
          - Lino Martinez - Memos (Box 8, Folder 29)
          - CARE Contract Information (Box 8, Folder 30)
          - Judith Weld, Memos (Box 8, Folder 31)
          - Judith Weld, RFPs (Box 9, Folder 1)
          - Monitoring Information (Box 9, Folder 2)
          - Research Branch (Box 9, Folder 3)
          - Health Resources & Services Branch (HRSB) (Box 9, Folder 4)
            Later became Health Services Branch (HSB).
          - Health Services Branch MOU With San Francisco General Hospital (SFGH) (Box 9, Folder 5)
          - Surveillance (Box 9, Folder 6)
          - Surveillance, AIDS Case Projections Through 1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
          - "HIV Incidence & Prevalence in SF in 1992; a Summary Report from an HIV Consensus Meeting", February 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
          - Prevention (Box 9, Folder 9)
          - Prevention and Youth Budgets (Box 9, Folder 10)
          - Prevention MOU with SFGH, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
          - Needle Exchange (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
          - Federal Audit of AIDS Office, Fiscal Year 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
          - Health Commission Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 15)
          - CDC Funding Awards, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
          - Distribution of AIDS Money by Ethnicity, Target Population (Box 9, Folder 17)
          - CARE Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
          - African American AIDS Leadership Group (Box 9, Folder 19)
          - African American HIV/AIDS Service Providers (Box 9, Folder 20)
          - James Loyce, Advisor to A.I.D.S. (Box 9, Folder 21)
          - AIDS Dementia Residential Care, "Chateau Agape" (Box 9, Folder 22)
          - AIDS Benefits Counselors (Box 9, Folder 23)
          - Ark of Refuge Application, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
          - Black Coalition on AIDS (Box 9, Folder 25)
          - Hospice by the Bay (Box 9, Folder 26)
          - St Mary's Hospital, Dementia Care (Box 9, Folder 27)
        - Troubleshooting Files, 1988-1992
          Arranged alphabetically by name of organization.